{
  "setCode": "isd",
  "cardDataUrl": "https://www.mtgsalvation.com/spoilers/filter?SetID=100&IncludeUnconfirmed=true&CardsPerRequest=999",
  "imagesUrl": "https://magic.wizards.com/en/articles/archive/feature/innistrad-card-image-gallery-2011-08-29",
  "exceptions": [
    {
      "_comments": [
        "add a new card = add:true, newValues {}",
        "delete a card  = delete:true, where",
        "update card(s) = where, newValues {}"
      ]
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Cloistered Youth",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Cloistered Youth (Unholy Fiend)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0008:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Unholy Fiend",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Unholy Fiend (Cloistered Youth)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0008",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Thraben Militia",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Thraben Militia (Thraben Sentry)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0038:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Thraben Sentry",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Thraben Sentry (Thraben Militia)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0038",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Homicidal Brute",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Homicidal Brute (Civilized Scholar)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0047:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Civilized Scholar",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Civilized Scholar (Homicidal Brute)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0047",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Delver of Secrets",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Delver of Secrets (Insectile Aberration)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0051:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Insectile Aberration",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Insectile Aberration (Delver of Secrets)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0051",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Ludevic's Abomination",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Ludevic's Abomination (Ludevic's Test Subject)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0064:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Ludevic's Test Subject",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Ludevic's Test Subject (Ludevic's Abomination)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0064",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Bloodline Keeper",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Bloodline Keeper (Lord of Lineage)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0090:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Lord of Lineage",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Lord of Lineage (Bloodline Keeper)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0090",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Screeching Bat",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Screeching Bat (Stalking Vampire)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0114:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Stalking Vampire",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Stalking Vampire (Screeching Bat)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0114",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Bane of Hanweir",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Bane of Hanweir (Hanweir Watchkeep)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0145:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Hanweir Watchkeep",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Hanweir Watchkeep (Bane of Hanweir)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0145",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Instigator Gang",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Instigator Gang (Wildblood Pack)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0149:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Wildblood Pack",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Wildblood Pack (Instigator Gang)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0149",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Kruin Outlaw",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Kruin Outlaw (Terror of Kruin Pass)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0152:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Terror of Kruin Pass",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Terror of Kruin Pass (Kruin Outlaw)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0152",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Merciless Predator",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Merciless Predator (Reckless Waif)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0159:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Reckless Waif",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Reckless Waif (Merciless Predator)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0159",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Rampaging Werewolf",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Rampaging Werewolf (Tormented Pariah)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0165:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Tormented Pariah",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Tormented Pariah (Rampaging Werewolf)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0165",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Ironfang",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Ironfang (Village Ironsmith)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0168:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Village Ironsmith",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Village Ironsmith (Ironfang)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0168",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Daybreak Ranger",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Daybreak Ranger (Nightfall Predator)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0176:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Nightfall Predator",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Nightfall Predator (Daybreak Ranger)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0176",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Garruk Relentless",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Garruk Relentless (Garruk, the Veil-Cursed)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0181:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Garruk, the Veil-Cursed",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Garruk, the Veil-Cursed (Garruk Relentless)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0181",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Gatstaf Howler",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Gatstaf Howler (Gatstaf Shepherd)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0182:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Gatstaf Shepherd",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Gatstaf Shepherd (Gatstaf Howler)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0182",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Grizzled Outcasts",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Grizzled Outcasts (Krallenhorde Wantons)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0185:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Krallenhorde Wantons",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Krallenhorde Wantons (Grizzled Outcasts)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0185",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Howlpack Alpha",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Howlpack Alpha (Mayor of Avabruck)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0193:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Mayor of Avabruck",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Mayor of Avabruck (Howlpack Alpha)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0193",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Ulvenwald Mystics",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Ulvenwald Mystics (Ulvenwald Primordials)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0208:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Ulvenwald Primordials",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Ulvenwald Primordials (Ulvenwald Mystics)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0208",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "where": "title='Howlpack of Estwald",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Howlpack of Estwald (Villagers of Estwald)",
        "mtgenIdBack": "isd|0209:a",
        "doubleFaceFrontCard": true
      }
    },
    {
      "where": "title='Villagers of Estwald",
      "newValues": {
        "title": "Villagers of Estwald (Howlpack of Estwald)",
        "mtgenIdFront": "isd|0209",
        "doubleFaceBackCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "_comment": "select all above-selected double-faced cards",
      "where": "isSelected=true",
      "newValues": {
        "useCardDataImg": true,
        "doubleFaceCard": true
      }
    },

    {
      "_comment": "Consider everything left the main set.",
      "where": "",
      "newValues": {
        "mainSet": true
      }
    }
  ]
}